<resources>
    <string name="app_name">quick news</string>
    <string name="news_content">Apple unveiled the iPhone 16 series on September 9, 2024, introducing four models: iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Plus, iPhone 16 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro Max. The standard iPhone 16 starts at $799, while the Pro version begins at $999.NDTVPROFIT.COM
                                Key Features:
                                Design and Display: The iPhone 16 and 16 Plus retain 6.1-inch and 6.7-inch screens, respectively. The Pro models feature slightly larger displays, with the iPhone 16 Pro at 6.3 inches and the Pro Max at 6.9 inches, achieved by reducing bezel size.
                                SPECDECODER.COM
                                Camera Enhancements: A new Camera Control button allows quick access to camera settings. The Pro models boast a 48-megapixel ultra-wide camera and a 5x telephoto lens, enhancing photography and videography capabilities.
                                SPECDECODER.COM
                                Performance: The iPhone 16 and 16 Plus are powered by the A18 Bionic chip, while the Pro models utilize the A18 Pro chip, offering improved speed and efficiency.
                                NDTVPROFIT.COM
                                Apple Intelligence: The series introduces "Apple Intelligence," an AI-driven feature enhancing Siri and offering advanced text generation and photo editing capabilities.
                                WSJ.COM
                                Availability in Bangladesh:
                                Executive Machines Limited, an Apple Authorized Reseller in Bangladesh, announced the launch of the iPhone 16 series on October 18, 2024. Pricing starts at Tk. 1,69,999 for the iPhone 16, Tk. 1,84,999 for the 16 Plus, Tk. 2,09,999 for the 16 Pro, and Tk. 2,49,999 for the 16 Pro Max. Customers can enjoy complimentary gifts worth Tk. 12,000 and 0% EMI options up to 24 months, along with cashback offers up to BDT 25,000 with select banks.
                                THEFRONTPAGEBD.COM
                                The iPhone 16 series brings notable advancements in design, performance, and AI capabilities, catering to a wide range of users..
    </string>
    <string name="news_content2">Despite the emergence of DeepSeek, a Chinese AI startup that developed a competitive AI model with a modest investment of approximately $6 million, tech giants like Microsoft and Meta are steadfast in their substantial AI investments. Microsoft has allocated $80 billion for AI in its current fiscal year, while Meta has committed up to $65 billion. Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella emphasized that increased spending is necessary to meet the growing demand for AI services. Similarly, Meta\'s leadership underscores the importance of significant investment to maintain a competitive edge in the rapidly evolving AI landscape. </string>
</resources>